comparably.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy | Comparably

## Comparably, Inc. Privacy Policy Effective Date: January 25, 2016

Welcome to the website of Comparably, Inc. (" **Comparably** ", " **we** ", " **us** " and/or " **our** "). We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect and disclose information and data when you use the Comparably website (" **Site** ") and Comparably services, including any software, mobile applications, or other services offered by Comparably from time to time and other products or services offered by third parties using Comparably functionality (collectively, " **Services** "). " **You** " refers to you as a user of the Site or Services.

 **BY USING THE SITE OR SERVICES YOU CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

### Managing Your Information Preferences

You can always review, correct, or update your Personal Information by changing the relevant settings in your Comparably account. You can opt out of receiving certain emails by changing notification settings on the Site or in our applications, clicking the unsubscribe link provided in an email, or by emailing us at info@comparably.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@comparably.com.

### Information We Collect

 _Personal Information_

We will collect information that you provide and that personally identifies you. Because we may change our offerings and features from time to time, the personal information that we ask you to provide us also may change but some examples of personal information we may ask you to provide may include: your name, email address, gender and other personally identifiable information when you sign up for the Site or Services (" **Personal Information** "). If you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Site or Services. We may also collect Personal Information from you when you access the Services and/or other parts of the Site and elect to provide Personal Information.

 _Non-Personal Information_

We may collect additional information that you provide but that does not personally identify you. Because we may change our offerings and features from time to time, the non-personal information that we ask you to provide us also may change but some examples of non-personal information we may ask you to provide may include: the name of the company that you work for, the number of employees that work for the company, your job title, your salary and benefit information and other information that is not intended to identify you personally (" **Non-Personal Information** "). If you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Site or Services. We may also collect Non-Personal Information from you when you access the Services and/or other parts of the Site and elect to provide that Non-Personal Information.

 _Mobile Application_

Our mobile application may collect certain additional information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the application. We may also use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location. If you do not want us to have your location information, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application.

 _Usage Data and Site Activity_

" **Usage Data** " is information or content we collect about the use of our Site or Services in a way that does not identify an individual user. Usage Data helps us understand trends in our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor or enhance our Services. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of Usage Data, and we may share Usage Data with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand our users' needs and to improve our Services. For example, each time you use the Site we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, the pages you view, how you interact with links on the Services and the time and duration of your visits to the Site. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors or users of our Site or application, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, etc.

 _Cookies and Web Beacons_

We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We may also use Web beacons (a file placed on a website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Site and Services, such as pre-populating your username for easier login. We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. At this time, Comparably does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking, including "do-not-track" signals. You can remove persistent cookies and change your privacy preferences by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, as further explained below.

### How We Use Information and When We May Share and Disclose Information Generally

We may use your Personal Information for the purpose for which it was provided, including without limitation for the purposes described further below:

  * Provision and Monitoring of the Services: We will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to and to support your use of the Services. We will also give you the opportunity to store, review and edit Personal Information and other information on the Site.
  * Surveys or Special Offers: From time to time, we may offer our users the opportunity to participate in surveys and other special offers. If you elect to participate in these services, you will need to provide certain Personal Information.
  * Questions and Requests: If you contact us by e-mail or otherwise, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem.
  * Contacting You About Other Products, Services and Events: Comparably may use your Personal Information to contact you in the future to tell you about products, services and events that may be of interest to you.
  * Research and Data Analysis: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Site and the Services, Comparably may perform data analysis and create statistical data based on the Non-Personal Information and Usage Data and other information provided to us. This data may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Comparably may share this data with its users as well as advertisers, researchers, business partners, publications, and other third parties. **This information will not identify you personally**.
  * Service Improvement: We may use Non-Personal Information and Usage Data collected through the Site and Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site and to improve the Services.

### Third Party Services and Applications

Through the Site or Services, you may elect to access third-party services and applications, such as LinkedIn, Facebook and other social networks. When you do so, you may be able to import information from those other services and applications and share content with those services. Some of those third-party services may also provide us with information from your accounts, which may enable us to enhance and personalize your use of the Site and Services. If you elect to enable such third-party services or applications, the information you share with such third-party services and applications will be subject to their privacy policies and your privacy settings. You can control whether your activity is sent to third-party services and applications by changing the relevant settings in your Comparably account. You also may be able to control or block such sharing by changing your privacy settings in such services or applications. Please note that third parties may collect, but we do not authorize them to collect, personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Site or Services.

### Service Providers

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses that we believe to be trustworthy and have privacy practices consistent with ours (" **Service Providers** "). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by Comparably.

### Advertising

We may work with third-party advertisers, search providers, and ad networks (" **Advertisers** "). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Site or Services in a way that does not identify you personally in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Site, the Services, or third-party websites and online services. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that Advertisers may collect from you or that you choose to provide to them.

### Other Transfers

We may share Personal Information, Non-Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Comparably. If Comparably is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets or equity, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information, Non-Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Comparably will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other content and information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Comparably or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

### Be Careful When You Share Information with Others

Please be aware that if you elect to share information on a public forum on the Site or Services, others may access that information. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

### Exclusions

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Comparably through the Site or Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as bulletin boards, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, " **Unsolicited Information** "). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Comparably shall be free, and you hereby grant Comparably the right, to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

### Security

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information and other information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk.

### Links

Our Site and Services may contain links or integrate with other websites and online services, or allow others to send you such links. Comparably is not responsible or liable for any damage or loss related to your use of any third-party website or online service. You should always read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of a third-party website or online service before using it, whether directly or in connection with your use of the Site or Services.

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

### Processing in the United States

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. By using our Site or Services, you agree that the applicable laws in the United States will govern the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location.

### Privacy Policy Changes

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will give you notice by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and application and by notifying you using the contact information provided by you (if any) and/or by posting a notice on the Site and application. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Site or Services, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

 **PLEASE PRINT A COPY OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR YOUR RECORDS AND PLEASE CHECK THE SITE FREQUENTLY FOR ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**
